{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Tell me ______ happened!",
      "a": "who",
      "b": "which",
      "c": "what",
      "d": "that",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- What:  used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "____.",
      "a": "Who are you talking about?",
      "b": "Whose are you talking?",
      "c": "Of who are you talking?",
      "d": "Of whom are you talking?",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action) \n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) \n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "That's the pen ______ I like.",
      "a": "who",
      "b": "which",
      "c": "whom",
      "d": "whose",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- We prefer which when the number of choices is limited",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This was ______ is I wanted to tell you.",
      "a": "who",
      "b": "that",
      "c": "which",
      "d": "what",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n- What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Did you hear ______ she said?",
      "a": "that",
      "b": "what",
      "c": "who",
      "d": "which",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n- What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Did you hear ______ she said to me?",
      "a": "what",
      "b": "whose",
      "c": "which",
      "d": "whom",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n- \"Whom\" refers to someone who is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The party, ______ you enjoyed so much, ended at 4 a.m.",
      "a": "who",
      "b": "whose",
      "c": "whom",
      "d": "which",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action)\n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action)\n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to)\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The girl ______ came was very pretty.",
      "a": "who",
      "b": "which",
      "c": "whom",
      "d": "what",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- \"Who\" is a Subject Pronoun (do an action)\n- \"Whom\" is an Object Pronoun (receive an action)\n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them\n- What:  used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain\n- What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the house ______ roof is green.",
      "a": "what",
      "b": "whose",
      "c": "which",
      "d": "whom",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- \"Whose\" is a Possessive Pronoun (Possessive forms tell us the person something belongs to) \n- Which: used to ask or talk about one or more members of a group of people or things, when you are uncertain about it or about them \n- What: used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain \n- \"Whom\" refers to someone who is an Object Pronoun (receive an action) ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "____.",
      "a": "What did happen?",
      "b": "What happened?",
      "c": "What did you happen?",
      "d": "What did happened?",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- What:  used to introduce a clause about something that is or was not known or not certain\n- What is preferred when the number of choices is unlimited",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "49",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}